Encoded By " Pirata-Tuga " ... TuGAZx ... Enjoy it !
Bjorling ...
Suliotis ?
Almost . Bjorling is easy .
Tebaldi ?
Bingo !
It 's my turn now .
- Don 't look ! - But I 'm not looking .
Did Daddy look ?
Is that true ?
Oh , God !
Gigli !
That 's obvious ! But what 's the piece ?
Never heard it !
Is it new ?
Seems to be .
Well , darling ?
I 'd say Handel .
Right . But what is it ?
No idea !
Well ?
I give up . What is it ?
Three-two to me !
So , what is it ?
Now get your hands off !
Just listen !
" FUNNY GAMES "
That 's cheating !
Sorry ?
It 's cheating to be practicing .
We 've booked for 10 : 00 tomorrow morning . You are coming ?
Yes , sure .
We 'll put the boat in the water first .
Can you give us a hand ? Let 's say , in 20 minutes ?
Sure ! Yes , I 'll be there in 20 minutes .
Okay . Thanks .
See you in a tick .
What 's up with him ?
No idea .
He seems in a huff .
She didn 't say a word .
Who did you arrange to play with tomorrow ?
Her .
Yesterday ?
The day before .
Well ?
Nothing . She was totally normal .
Sissi isn 't there .
Maybe she was just in the house . Or at the beach .
Who were the two laddies ?
How should I know ?
They 're probably relatives . I think his brother has a son that age .
Don 't put that there ! Take your things upstairs !
Okay .
Do it now !
Don 't leave things in the entrance , or someone will trip over .
There 's still so much left in the car .
Are you listening ?
I 'm going !
Open the windows , will you . We need to let some air in .
Okay , Mom !
Stop it , Rolfi ! Stop it !
Go on , get down !
I have to unpack !
Go on , get out !
- Georg ? - Yes ?
Where 's the other box with the food ?
I 'll bring it right away .
The golf gear was in the way . I put it in the Rover last .
We 'd better get them in quick ! The things have got really hot !
This cool-box is totally useless .
Stop it now , you 'll knock me over .
- The butter 's all soft . - Go see your mistress .
There 're some cold cuts in the other box .
I 'll get it . I 'll just open the windows .
Leave the shutters closed on the lake side , or it 'll be too hot .
Stop that . You 'll get something
in a minute , I must just put this away .
Can 't you call the dog ? He won 't let me put the things away .
Rolfi !
Come here !
Come and see your master !
And the bottles too , otherwise it 'll all be warm by the evening .
Stop it , Rolfi !
Be quiet !
Come in !
Sorry . He 's off his head .
Hello .
Thanks for coming . It 'd have been tough on our own .
- No problem ! This is ... - Paul . Nice to meet you .
Paul is son of a business colleague .
- It 's a pleasure . Nice of you to help . - Mine too .
I mean , the pleasure 's mine .
- Not so much his . - Will you be quiet ?
Lunatic !
- Get into the house , go on ! - Come here , Rolfi !
- When did you get out here ? - Last week .
You too ?
- Yes . - No .
They didn 't arrive till the weekend . We came on Friday .
Hello , Fred !
Nice of you to come over right away .
- How 's Eva ? - Fine .
- Hello . - Hello , madam .
... and where 's Tropea ?
In south Italy . Right at the tip ,
- almost on the toes of the boot . - But it 's even hotter there .
Not necessarily .
Last year when I was in Italy it was freezing
and here you were swimming , right ?
But it 's a shame Sissi isn 't here . Without her , it 's less fun .
- Be careful ! - I am !
Careful , or the overhauling will have been for nothing .
Look , you can 't see anything !
Good .
Can you help me lift the boom over ?
Mind the halyard !
But she said she 'd be there for the whole holiday .
Listen , my boy . I don 't know why she isn 't there either .
Maybe she went to Tropea with a school friend . I don 't know .
Tomorrow we 'll go over and ask her mother . She 's bound to explain all .
Now stop moping ...
Why was Uncle Fred so strange ?
I 'm not surprised !
She got pretty worked up about it last time .
Forget it , please .
She won 't change , and you 'll just get in a state .
Exactly !
That 's it !
Great . They 're outside working on the boat .
What ?
5 : 00 or 5 : 30 . I don 't know the time here ,
I mean , the kitchen clock has stopped .
I must get a new battery on Monday .
What ?
Yes , that 's what I 'm doing now .
Some fillets .
Yes , you know , it 's crazy . The whole thing
defrosted and now it needs eating .
Come out and see us !
No , really , like a fool , I froze three pounds of beef fillet at once ,
and now here I am .
No , I 'm not joking . Come and spend the weekend .
What ?
He shouldn 't make such a fuss . Hold on .
We need a sharp knife .
I 'd like to see it again some day . Tell Dad .
Sorry .
Tell your beloved to pack up his laptop ,
get in the car , and you 'll be here in two hours at the most !
He shouldn 't be so elusive .
Okay . Think about it .
In any case , there 's enough steak here for a week .
Bye , Fanny .
Say , give us another ring anyway
to tell us whether we can expect you .
Yes , bye .
- What is it now ? - Someone 's here .
- Where ? - At the door .
Hello ?
Hello . Sorry to disturb you .
I 'm from next door .
We saw each other when you stopped the car at the gate .
Oh , yes , we did .
Come in , please .
Hurry up , we 're eating in 10 minutes !
So what is it ?
Well ...
Eva sent ...
I mean , Mrs. Berlinger sent me .
She 's just cooking ...
and she 's run out of eggs . She wonders if you can help her out .
But of course .
- How many does she need ? - Four .
Four ?
- What for ? - Sorry ?
What for ?
What does she need the eggs for ?
I mean , what 's she making ?
No idea .
Are they okay like that or shall I wrap them ?
As you like .
So how did you get in ?
At the front . I mean , by the beach .
But you didn 't get wet at all !
There 's a hole in the fence ,
by the water , not in the water .
Fred knows -
I mean , Mr. Berlinger knows it . He showed me it .
I see . Okay .
So , wrapped , or is this okay ?
No , no , that 's fine , no problem .
- Many thanks . - You 're welcome .
Love to Eva . Look forward to the golf tomorrow !
I 'll tell her . Thanks again .
And thanks again to Fred and your friend -
- Damn it ! - What 's up ?
It 's not a disaster .
Hang on .
Thank God , we just arrived ...
and I must shop in the village on Monday .
I 'm really embarrassed .
It 's nothing . No one here eats eggs for breakfast anyway ,
so it 's not a major problem .
That 's a relief , thank you .
I should just have been more careful .
- I put my left hand - - Well , no point in crying over spilt milk .
You 're really kind .
One does one 's best .
I 'm really sorry .
I 'm very clumsy , you know .
I think I 've got two left hands .
So you 're ideal for carrying eggs .
Yes , you could say .
Well ...
And what are we going to do now ?
We do have steak , but we might be getting visitors ,
and they 're bound to want eggs for breakfast .
But you 'll have four left .
After all , I did see you had a box of twelve , right ?
You 're right .
Shouldn 't I wrap them up ?
No need .
Are you sure ?
If you want to .
If I want to ?
Well , maybe it is better after all .
- Oh , no ! - What 's the matter ?
Oh , no !
I 'm sorry .
Before you destroy the rest of the kitchen ,
maybe you should take your eggs and leave .
Well ...
Here you are .
Won 't you wrap them ?
I 'm really sorry .
Honestly .
Me too .
There .
- Here you are . - Many thanks . Thank you .
I 'll tell Mrs. Berlinger how nice you were .
Okay . Do as you see fit .
- Bye . - Good-bye .
Excuse me ?
Stop it ! Rolfi !
Excuse me !
Off you go !
Get lost !
I mean now !
I 'm sorry . He 's completely harmless .
- He just wants to have a game . - Funny game .
Did he hurt you ?
Peter 's just afraid of dogs .
- I 'm sorry . - Me too .
He jumped up on me .
I 'm sorry about that .
Well .
Shall I lock him in so you can leave ?
- No need . - I can tell my husband to -
There 's really no need , thanks .
It 's my fault . I quite forgot the dog .
Otherwise , I 'd have come to fetch the ...
Oh ! What a wonderful kit !
Gallaway , isn 't it ?
It 's fantastic .
May I ?
We hardly stand a chance for tomorrow !
Good clubs don 't make good golfers .
That 's true , yes .
Would it be cheeky of me to ask if I can try it just once ?
Right now , outside ?
Please ! Okay ?
From the lawn out to the lake , okay ?
- If it makes you happy . I - - Thanks .
Excuse me .
He loves golf !
- We both do . - Sorry ?
Both of us . We both love golf .
Rolfi !
Stop it !
Be quiet now !
What 's up ?
I don 't know , probably it 's too hot for him too .
I 'll go and see .
Brilliant !
Like the difference between day and night .
Thanks very much .
You 're welcome .
Where 's Tom ?
- Who ? - Did you give him the eggs ?
Sorry ?
The driver is absolutely top-class .
You must try it .
Listen , young man .
I don 't know what game you 're playing , but I 'm not going to join in .
Will you go now , please ?
What game ?
Sorry , madam , but I don 't understand
why you 're suddenly so unfriendly .
Have Tom or I done anything to annoy you ?
Please , would you leave ?
Did you behave badly while I was outside ?
Was he cheeky ?
- Did he say anything - - That 's enough .
I asked you to leave , so ...
please go .
Okay .
I don 't understand what 's upset you so , but if you insist ...
Fine .
Give the eggs to Tom and we won 't bother you again .
I 'm sorry ?
Of course we 'll be telling Eva and Fred .
Honestly , I 've never experienced anything like it before .
What about you , Tom ?
May we have the eggs now , please ?
I told you to leave !
Did I do something wrong ...
Now just get out of here , you ...
Is the dog with you ? What 's going on ?
- Get them out ! - Good to see you , Mr. Schober .
You are Mr. Schober , right ?
Fred , I mean , Mr. Berlinger told me .
What ? What 's the matter ?
- Throw him out ! - Your wife 's mistaken .
I 'm very glad you 're here .
I 'm sure you can clarify the misunderstanding .
- Daddy , I can 't - - Please , Georg !
It 's outrageous !
Can I explain how this misunderstanding arose ?
Mrs. Berlinger sent me over to fetch some eggs .
So what ? And then ?
Your wife gave the eggs to Peter , but he smashed them .
Yes . And she gave me four more eggs , but ...
then the dog jumped up on me ...
and now ...
But it was a 12-pack , and you 're shopping Monday anyway ...
We just want the eggs ,
that 's all .
Can you tell me what 's going on ?
Give them the eggs .
Hold on ! Can you wait a moment ?
- Can I take them ? - Just a moment .
What 's going on ?
It can 't just be about these ridiculous eggs . Why this rage ?
I 'm not justifying myself to these ...
I asked you to throw them out . I must have my reasons .
Do as you wish . For me , the subject is closed .
Anna ?
Would you please leave ?
My wife doesn 't feel well .
I can 't act as arbitrator in a matter I don 't know anything about .
Please , would you leave ?
What is it ?
If you don 't mind ?
So give them to him !
What 's going on ?
Nothing 's going on .
She gave him the eggs , the dog jumped on him , he smashed them .
He wants more . Is it so complicated ?
What kind of tone is that supposed to be ?
Watch I don 't smash your balls as well !
Now get out ! Right now !
Is it broken ?
Be good , now .
Behave yourself !
Be nice !
I don 't want to hurt you , but behave yourself !
Please stay where you are .
Please stay there !
- He hit me in the face . - Yes . He started it .
You can help him if you want , but no messing about .
- Bring him a chair . - My knee !
- He should take off his pants and sit down . - A chair !
Peter studies medicine . He 'll fix it .
Take off your pants , please .
If you won 't let me see your wound , I can 't help you .
Sorry I hurt you ,
but you left me no choice , you must admit .
Be reasonable , Mr. Schober . Let him look at your leg .
He 's sure to be able to help .
Will you leave please ?
Please !
This won 't get us anywhere .
You must let him help you . You haven 't any choice .
You 're a ship 's captain , sir .
You know that on board ship , the Captain 's word is final .
So , what do you want to do , sir ?
Do you want to call someone ? An ambulance ?
Or the police ?
Go on ! I won 't stop you . Nor will Tom .
That 's a promise !
Right ?
What are you waiting for ?
He dropped the mobile in the water .
Why are you doing this ?
Why not ?
Okay , then , another game .
A guessing game .
What 's this ?
A golf ball .
Exactly , sir , a golf ball .
And why do I have it here in my pocket ?
The lady knows .
Because ...
Well ?
- Because you didn 't hit it . - Exactly !
And why didn 't I hit it ?
Because you were stopped .
Exactly .
And because I had to test the club another way .
Where is he ?
Cold .
Colder .
Warmer .
Hotter .
Cold .
Really cold .
Warmer , hotter , boiling !
Would you kindly get me some food from the kitchen ?
Would it be possible ?
Bananas or something like that .
And don 't think of picking up a knife or something .
I 'd be sorry if you did .
For your sake .
The sun 's coming out again .
Very kind of you . Thank you .
Hello ! Sweetie !
Where are you ?
Come on down !
We 're both thinking the same , aren 't we ?
We saw your boat !
Hello , Gerda ! Hello , Robert !
How long have you been here ?
Not long .
We 're still unpacking .
How long are you staying ?
A week or two .
We 're not sure yet .
Great !
- Hello , darling , lovely to see you . - Hello .
Have you met my sister ?
No ! Pleased to meet you !
Hello , Robert !
- Everything okay ? - Of course .
This is Paul . He 's living with our neighbors .
- Hello , Paul ! - Hello , pleased to meet you !
Are you cold ?
No , I have eczema .
You should go swimming . The water here does wonders for you .
Thank you for the tip .
Hello .
How 's Georg ?
Very well , thank you !
So where is he ?
He pulled a muscle putting the mast up .
So he 's lying down .
That 's a real shame .
That 's the result of doing everything yourself .
Robert wouldn 't dream of putting our boat
in the water on his own , right ?
Tell your beloved to pull himself together .
We barbecue nearly every night . We can 't do without him .
I 'll tell him !
I mean it . As soon as he 's better , come and see us right away .
Robert 's son is here with his girlfriend . He 'll like her .
Right then .
Have a good time , darling .
If the wind doesn 't change , bring the car .
The weather forecast says wind .
For tomorrow .
- I said to Robert we 'd get nowhere . - Where are you moored ?
What ?
Oh ! Over there , behind the headland .
But on the other side .
- The wooden house covered in ivy ? - That 's it .
- It looks very pretty . - Indeed it is , young man .
Right then . Bye !
- Are you staying all week ? - This week , sure .
Might see you tonight !
As you like . We 're always pleased to see you !
I don 't know yet .
- We 'll see how Georg is . - Yes , you see ! See you soon !
They 'll be here in two hours at the latest ...
and then this farce will be over .
Sorry , but that 's not quite true .
I heard the end of your phone call .
You asked your friends to call you back if they were coming tonight .
Or did I misunderstand you ?
Even if they can 't reach us , they 'll still come .
Is lying allowed ?
Just a moment !
There you are . Please .
You really can speak to us openly .
You 'll feel much better . We 're also being very open with you .
Perhaps try putting a cushion under it .
If you 'd accepted Peter 's help , it would be hurting less .
I 'm quite willing to help you .
But I don 't want to impose .
Careful !
Yes , raise the leg . That 's bound to be more comfortable .
There we are ! Done !
Can you leave it out , you bastards ?
Is that an offer ?
- What ? - Using our first names ?
I 'm very happy about that .
It does vastly simplify our communication .
I 'd still like to apologize for just now ,
for being too familiar ,
but you must admit that the smack was
an unreasonable reaction nonetheless .
Paul .
This is Peter .
Come here , Tom . Have you no manners ?
Give Georg your hand .
Here , it 's for the pain .
What ? To you , we 're non-existent ?
- Being on familiar terms doesn 't mean - - You bastard ...
Quiet ! Please !
Stop !
Stop it now , otherwise your mother will get it , do you understand ?
Understand ?
Keep quiet now .
What a scene , just for being on first-name terms !
We were only trying to improve relations .
- I thought we could - - Why are you doing that ?
Fatty , why are you doing that ?
Go on , tell us !
I don 't know . I ...
The Captain wants to know .
Why ?
Well ?
It 's difficult to talk about it . I ...
Don 't be shy .
You know just how hard it is ...
My God , what a fuss !
His father got a divorce ...
when he was still that tiny ,
- and he took another woman - - That 's not true !
He 's lying !
It was my mother who divorced ...
because ...
I ...
Because she wanted to have her little teddy all to herself ,
and since then , he 's been a queer and a crook .
You see ?
You 're an asshole !
The truth is , he comes from a filthy , deprived family ,
he has five brothers and sisters
who are all drug addicts .
His dad 's an alcoholic ,
and as for his mother , you can imagine .
Or rather , the truth is , it 's him who fucks her .
Tough ,
but true .
Come on , calm down now .
You 're disgusting . Can 't you cut out
your obscenities in front of the child ?
Oh ! Sorry .
Of course . What answer would you like ?
What would satisfy you ?
Anyway , what I said isn 't true . You know that as well as I.
Look at him .
Do you really think he comes from a deprived background ?
Right .
He 's a spoiled little shit-face ,
tormented by ennui and world-weariness ,
weighed down by the void of existence !
That 's hard , honestly !
You see , he 's smiling again .
Right .
Satisfied ?
Or another version ?
I 'm hungry .
I 'll see what there is .
You see , the truth is , he 's a drug addict .
That 's why he 's going now , and ...
That 's why he has bad nerves , you see .
Me too , I 'm a drug addict .
Together we rob rich families in smart houses
so we can afford the stuff .
Can you stop this lunacy ?
I get the message ,
isn 't that enough for you ?
You get the message ?
Great !
Fatty ! He 's got it !
Now he knows everything !
That 's fantastic , really .
Listen .
Peter , come in here !
Listen , we 're going to bet , okay ?
Sit down , come on !
- It 's dark in here . - Now don 't fall asleep !
We 'll bet that -
What 's the time ?
Twenty to 9 : 00 .
That in , let 's say , 12 hours ...
all three of you 'll be kaput .
What ?
You bet us , that tomorrow at 9 : 00 , you 'll be alive ,
and we bet you , you 'll be dead , okay ?
They don 't want to bet .
That 's no good . You have to bet .
What do you think ? Do you think they 've a chance of winning ?
You are on their side , aren 't you ?
So , who will you bet with ?
What kind of bet is this ?
Dead , they can give nothing , and conversely , they can win nothing .
They 'll lose in any case . Obviously .
Stop this nonsense .
Are you trying to scare us ?
Isn 't what you 've done already enough ?
What do you want ? Our money ?
Help yourselves and get out .
Don 't you think Fred and Eva might come and see what 's going on ?
And give us a good hiding , right ?
Okay .
As they say on TV :
The bets are placed !
And what 'll we do now ?
Could you kindly make us some food ?
You worry me , Fatty .
Can 't you control yourself ?
You 've just gobbled up the sausage .
It 's disgusting .
What are these people going to think ?
I haven 't eaten since lunchtime !
And stop calling me Fatty .
- Okay , Tom . - Okay , Jerry .
But can 't you pay some attention to your appearance ?
You think it makes you more attractive ?
Look at the Captain 's wife .
Do you think she finds you attractive ?
- With your flab ? - Stop it !
Look at her .
She 's not as old as all that .
Excuse me , madam .
You 'd be quite acceptable to her ,
but with that figure of yours !
Follow her example .
Her body 's really in shape .
Not a single extra calorie !
I 'm not so sure !
What ?
Did you hear that , madam ?
That 's really cheeky !
We can 't put up with that , can we ?
Hey you ! Indian !
What 's your name anyway ?
Georg .
Like Daddy .
Lovely !
Georgie-boy , come over to me .
Come here .
Come on . Sit down beside me . We 're going to play a game .
Let the boy go !
I know you don 't want to play , but you 'll see , it 's fun .
See how your mother 's standing up for you ?
- Dad could take an example from her ! - Stop it !
For that we 're going to let your mom play with us .
Hold Georgie a moment .
We 're playing a nice little game : Kitten in the Bag .
You 'll see , it 's fun .
There ! Don 't panic ! Nothing will happen .
I said this is a nice game .
A family game .
Daddy is playing too so he doesn 't get bored .
Right . Now listen !
You 'll have to keep still , or it 's no fun .
Hey ! Listen now !
That 's right , Georgie .
We 'll work together , okay ?
The pillow case isn 't uncomfortable , is it ?
You 've enough air , haven 't you ?
Yes .
Great . Then we can finally start .
So , the starting point of our game
was that mommy and our little Indian wanted to slip out of here .
- But why ? - Don 't know .
Is lying allowed , Fatty ?
What an example you 're setting ! You know why .
You mentioned her flab .
What do you mean , me ?
It was you who doubted her flawlessness !
Okay . Forget it !
I understand too how it embarrassed her . With the boy here .
That 's why we play " Kitten in the Bag . "
To preserve moral decency .
The kiddy wears a pillow case While mummy strips off , in great haste !
We mustn 't hurt the kitty cat , right ? Dad 's broken leg is enough .
Let the child go . Please !
Exactly . Daddy 's playing with us too .
What are we waiting for ?
Tell your wife not to be so shy . It 's ridiculous .
Anyway , I 'm sure she isn 't flabby .
Please , let the child go .
Please !
You only have to say to her , " Get undressed . "
I beg you !
" Get undressed , my darling . "
Get undressed .
Get undressed , my darling .
Well done .
What did I say ? Not an ounce of flab .
Now , let 's get dressed again .
Fatty , can you take the little piggy ?
He isn 't quite potty-trained .
Go and clean him up .
- Let the child go ! - I won 't do anything to him .
Will you sit down , please ?
I 'd advise you not to kick me .
I hope you won 't be too bored with these two .
Pour a pan of water over his head .
But make sure you don 't ruin the carpet .
No , no , of course that was a joke .
I have to retake Latin in the autumn .
If I pass it , then things will get moving . I 'll study commercial law .
But before that there 's military service .
Does it hurt a lot ?
Why don 't you kill us right away ?
Don 't forget the entertainment value .
We 'd all be deprived of our pleasure .
Sorry about your leg .
But it 's your fault , if I might say so .
Why did you smack Paul ?
For me , begging for the eggs to no avail was very unpleasant .
Humiliating , actually .
I don 't know if you realize that .
It 's just not worth it ,
all this charade , for a box of eggs .
They should still be there .
You should have trusted what your wife said .
She really begged you just to let us leave with the eggs .
Naturally one 's always wiser after the event .
Ah ! There they are !
One of them is cracked .
It 's not bad , what these boxes withstand . When you think -
Why are you doing that ?
How stupid do you think I am ?
I don 't understand . You 're really forcing me to treat you badly .
Jesus ! That 's it ! You 've done it now !
And Paul even said we should take care of the carpet !
Please , let us go !
You 're so young still !
You have all your life before you !
Nothing 's happened yet !
We 'll say ...
that Georg broke his leg in the boat .
- Everyone 'll believe it , and - - Please stop .
Why are you humiliating yourself ?
It 's just as unpleasant for me as for you .
Georgie ?
Where are you ?
Georgie !
I 'm coming !
Hold on , I 'll put on some music for us .
Don 't come any closer !
The trigger !
You have to prime the trigger !
And you need to pull it too !
Tralee trala , here we are !
Mommy !
Hello , my darling !
Is everything okay ?
They 've -
They 've killed Sissi !
- Hi , Beavis ! - Hi , Butt-Head !
- Everything under control ? - Looks like it .
May I ?
Please . Sure .
You must wonder , Captain , where this lovely rifle comes from .
Or does it seem familiar ?
Haven 't you ever been hunting with Fred ?
Do you know , your little darling just tried to kill me with it ?
Scarcely believable , but it 's the truth , and nothing but the truth .
Isn 't that right , Georgie ?
What do you say , Tom ?
Dreadful .
What 's the time ?
Just after 11 : 00 .
We should start thinking about our bet , don 't you think ?
Actually we ought to be grateful to Georgie for helping us .
One for Beavis ,
one for Butt-Head .
A , B , BOO and out go you !
You 're not leaving at this stage . First you 'll have to say your age .
Well ?
She doesn 't want to play .
Well , how old do you think she is ?
37 ?
No flab ...
So I 'd say ,
let 's be generous , let 's say 35 .
Agreed ?
She agrees .
Who are you going to start counting with ?
Her ?
And now I 'm going to get myself something to eat .
One , two , three ,
four , five , six , seven ...
Can I get anyone anything ?
You 're an idiot , Fatty .
You don 't shoot the person you 've
counted out , but the one that 's left over !
What 's wrong with you ?
- He tried to escape ! - So what ?
That 's no reason to get trigger-happy .
Have you no sense of timing ?
What 's the time ?
Just before 12 : 00 .
Shit .
We 'll get nothing from the others now .
- Let 's get out of here . - Fine .
Thanks so much for the driver . I 'll put it back in the bag , okay ?
Thanks .
So , have a good evening !
Good-bye !
Bye !
They 've gone .
Do you hear ? They 've gone !
I 'll get a knife .
Come on . Calm down now .
Take deep breaths .
Come on , darling .
Calm down now .
Calm yourself .
That 's it . Take some deep breaths .
We 've got to get out of here .
What if they come back ?
Do you think you can walk if I support you ?
I 'll try .
What 's wrong with your arm ?
Shall I try and make a splint for it ? Then I can hold you better .
No , it 's okay . Come on .
Let 's go .
Okay ?
No ! Anna !
No !
They 've locked the door .
We must use the window .
I can 't .
Georg !
- Please ! - I can 't manage it .
You go .
It 's crazy wasting so much time . Run for it . Please !
Climb out of the kitchen window .
Try to get as far as the inn , or ...
If we 're locked in here , the gate will be shut too .
That 's true .
Take a pair of pliers and cut the fence .
But careful on the road . Maybe they 're waiting out there .
Where are the pliers ?
I don 't know .
Here , in the kitchen .
No ,
down at the boat shed .
I can 't leave you alone here .
Go now , please !
Put some clothes on .
And shoes too , so you can run .
Hold on , the bag 's still here .
Down there .
I 'll hide down in the wine cellar .
The key must be in the door .
I 'll shut myself in and wait for you to come back .
How will you get down there ?
I 'll manage .
Go now ! Please !
The mobile ! It 's working again !
What ?
It 's working ! It 's obviously dried out .
- So get on the phone ! - Who to ?
Anyone ! The police !
What 's their number ?
No idea .
Call my mother ...
Your father - No , wait ...
Call Peter , he 's at home , I know , he wanted to -
Press four and then hit speed-dial .
It 's not ringing .
Let me listen .
But there is a signal !
Some of the contacts are probably still damp .
Nothing .
Get the hair dryer . Maybe it 'll help .
Can you pass me the chair ?
It won 't work .
Leave it , come on .
Maybe it 's permanently broken .
Get going !
We 're wasting far too much time . Let me do it .
Go on !
Pull me over there on the chair .
I think it 'll be easier than walking .
Thanks .
And now , run !
Please , forgive me !
It -
I love you !
Run , please !
Help !
Peter ? It 's Georg !
Can you hear me ? I can barely hear you !
Listen , if you can hear me ,
send the police over to our lake house , right away !
Hello ?
Shit !
Peter ! Can you hear me ?
Stop !
Missed !
Morning , Captain .
Morning .
They 'll be there any minute .
We 'll have to hurry then . Right , Beavis ?
Why don 't you believe me ?
- How old did we say ? 37 ? - 35 .
Good that the battery charger 's in the car !
- If it 's her age , you must start with her . - Why ?
- The battery was okay . - That 's the rules .
Okay , I 'll start with her .
Yes , I know .
It 's time you had another idea . The lady tried that trick before .
Count faster , Beavis .
Do you think we have no imagination ?
Without risk , you can 't have a bet , that 's obvious , Captain .
You must have a chance too .
The wind blows where it wishes .
That 's the joy of sailing , don 't you think ?
Right then !
... thirty-four , thirty-five !
Don 't make the same mistake again .
It 's the one that 's left who 's turn it is ,
not the one who 's counted out .
Hang on .
I can see a new toy .
I assume we owe this to the lady ?
This will make things a bit more amusing .
The dumb suffer in unspectacular fashion .
We want to offer the audience something ...
and show what we can do , right ?
You can join in again now .
We were already on first-name terms , right ?
So , Anna ,
now we 're going to play :
" The Loving Wife " , or ...
Whether by knife or whether by gun
Losing your life can sometimes be fun .
Hey ! No falling asleep !
You have to play with us , or you 'll be gagged again .
That 's not very nice , is it ?
So , here are the rules of the game :
Georgie senior has been counted out , so it 's his turn .
It 'll be hard to change that .
Unless you want to take his place .
Do you want to ?
I 'm sure Fatty will understand . Right , Fatty ?
Don 't call me Fatty .
- You see , he understands . - Get this over with . That 's enough .
That 's enough ?
You think that 's enough ?
What do you think , Anna ?
Have you had enough ? Or do you want to play some more ?
Don 't reply anymore .
Let them do what they want . Please !
Then it 'll be over quicker .
Huh , that 's cowardly !
We 're not up to feature film length yet .
Is that enough ?
But you want a real ending ,
with plausible plot development , don 't you ?
The bet is still on . It can 't be withdrawn unilaterally .
So :
the game is called : " The Loving Wife . "
Although Beavis has done the counting , she can choose ...
who will be next . And ...
using what implement !
Do we prefer the little knife ?
Or the rifle ?
Well then , what does the housewife say ?
Hello , wakey , wakey !
So , you 're not interested ?
You don 't want to play anymore .
Beavis , show her the game again .
Wait .
Here you are .
Hey , careful !
I almost cut myself .
Really ?
You see . It 's the little knife . You can spare him that .
You only have to play with us .
I understand , Anna .
I understand , really !
It 's not a good feeling , causing the one you love to suffer .
But it costs so little to avoid all that .
You only need follow the rules , and all will be well .
What must I do ?
You see , it wasn 't that difficult .
And we 'll make it easy too .
You recite a prayer of your choice .
If you say it flawlessly , God will help you
and you choose what happens next .
Or shall we carry on with Georgie senior ?
I don 't know a prayer .
You don 't know any prayers ?
Not a single prayer ?
Is that possible ?
Tell her one , Fatty .
Stop calling me Fatty all the time .
I 'll stop saying it . Well ?
Oh Lord and Father , make me kind , So I , in heaven , my place may find .
- That 's too easy . - I can 't think of any others .
Okay .
Oh Lord and Father , make me kind , So I , in heaven , my place may find .
No ! Not like that !
It 's a prayer .
You can 't just drone on like that .
You 're asking the Lord God for something . So pray properly .
Go on . Go down on your knees properly .
Go on ! Get on with it !
There . That 's right . Kneel down properly .
Put your hands together .
Not on your stomach .
Where is the one you pray to ? Up there !
You have to pray to the heavens ! That 's it !
Right , and now , in a fervent tone , if you don 't mind .
- Beavis , can you help her a little ? - No !
Oh Lord and Father , make me kind ,
So I , in heaven , my place may find .
Well done ! You did that well !
That was the trial run , and now we 're going for Olympic Gold :
If you can recite this prayer , which is sadly much too short ,
from back to front , without any mistakes ,
you can not only choose which of you kicks the bucket first ,
but also , and no doubt this will interest you more - how .
whether quick and painless by the bullet ...
Careful !
Where 's the remote ?
Where 's the fucking remote control ?
That was the trial run , and now we 're going for Olympic Gold :
If you can recite this prayer , which is sadly much too short ,
from back to front , without any mistakes ,
you can not only choose which of you kicks the bucket first ,
but also , and no doubt this will interest you more - how :
whether quick and painless by the bul -
You shouldn 't have done that , Anna . One doesn 't break the rules .
Sorry . You 've failed .
Say good-bye to Georgie .
Would you sit down ?
Can you give me your gloves ?
... only it 's all inverted .
But of course all these predictions are wrong so as to avoid a panic .
But now Kelvin knows how it really is ...
and wants to warn his wife and daughter in time .
But the problem is not only getting
from the world of antimatter to reality ,
- but also to regain communication - - Look !
Now that 's a sporting attitude !
Hey , look out , fatso !
I thought you were a non-swimmer .
Go and get the widow . She 'll feel lonely otherwise .
Would you mind cooperating ?
It 's not easy . Otherwise I might hurt you .
So . Where was I ?
The communication problems between matter and antimatter .
Exactly . As if you were in a black hole !
Gravitation is so strong that nothing can escape it : absolute silence .
- By the way , what 's the time ? - What ?
What 's the time ?
Just after eight .
Already ?
Why ?
The deadline was at 9 : 00 . She had almost an hour left !
Firstly , it was too hard to sail like that ,
- and secondly , I 'm starting to get hungry . - That 's true .
... when Kelvin overcomes gravitation ,
it turns out that one universe is real ,
but the other is just a fiction .
How does that happen ?
What do I know ! It was a kind of model projection in cyberspace .
And where is your hero now ? In reality or fiction ?
His family is in reality and he 's in fiction .
- But the fiction is real , isn 't it ? - How do you mean ?
- Well , you see it in the film , right ? - Of course .
So , it 's just as real as the reality which you see likewise , right ?
- Crap . - Why ?
Is anyone awake yet ?
Who is it ?
Good morning to you .
Sorry to disturb you so early , but I 've come from Anna 's .
And ?
Don 't you remember me ?
Yesterday afternoon , on the jetty . I 'm Paul .
Oh , yes .
- Good morning . - Morning .
Anna sent me . We had guests arrive unexpectedly this morning ...
and she wonders if you could spare her a few eggs ?
I think so .
Come in .
Wait a minute .
" I Hope you Enjoyed " " Released By TuGAZx " " PTpOWeR "
[ ENGLISH-US \ UK ]